kugli.com 2018-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Kugli.com

Last update: 2018-05-24

This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the Kugli.com work and to keep it safe (details below).

Kugli.com offers a number of features which may include a classified ads section and other sections.

Collection. Information posted on Kugli.com except your E-Mail Address is publicly available. We collect and store the following personal information:

* E-Mail Address, contact information (only if you create an account with us)  
* computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Kugli.com and ad data (all through cookies - you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site)  
* other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

Please also remember that if you choose to provide personally identifiable information using certain public features of our services, individuals reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines and other robots may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through our Services.

Kugli.com does store some information in "cookies" on your computer. If you use a section of our website that requires a login, your login information may be stored in a cookie for the duration of your browser session. If you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. This site or the advertisers on this site may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process.  
If you want to block the use and saving of cookies from the Site on to their computers hard drive, you should take the necessary steps within your web browserâs settings to block all cookies from the Site. Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain parts of our Site may not function correctly. For information on how to disable cookies, refer to your browserâs documentation.

Use. We use users' personal information to:

* provide our services  
* resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems  
* encourage safe trading and enforce our policies  
* customize users' experience, measure interest in our services and inform users about services and updates  
* communicate marketing and promotional offers to you  
* do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

When you use our services we may process your account data ("account data"). Account data may include your full name, email address, country, city, address, phone number, your ads you wish to promote to our visitors. The source of this data is you. The account data may be processed for the purposes of providing our services, communicating with you and allowing other members and non members to contact you and send leads to you (leads that you might be interested in or not). Certain account data (your name, your ads details) may be disclosed publicly on our website and other websites. The legal bases for this processing are \- consent \- our legitimate interests, namely the operation of our business model. Disclosure. We don't sell or rent users' personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with:

* corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to)  
* service providers who help with our business operations.

If you submit a classified ad all of the information except for your email address will be displayed for everyone to see (including the email address and other contact details you specify in your classified ad description).

If you make use of any section of our website that requires payment (ie: premium listings, or paid advertisements) we will collect the information necessary to conduct the transaction and that information may be shared with our vendors, contractors, etc only as necessary to complete the transaction. If you participate in a fraudulent transcation, attempt to, or abuse the services or network resources any and all information we have or can collect may be shared with anyone we feel is necessary to resolve the problem.

Any products and ads listed for sale are from independent parties and you must check directly with them regarding their provided policies.

Using Information from Kugli.com. You may use personal information gathered from Kugli.com only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that. Access, Modification, and Deletion. You can see, modify or erase your ad data (including personal information) by reviewing your posting or account status page or by contacting us through our contact forms.

Cookies: Kugli.com does store some information in "cookies" on your computer. If you use a section of our website that requires a login, your login information may be stored in a cookie for the duration of your browser session. If you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. This site or the advertisers on this site may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process.  
If you want to block the use and saving of cookies from the Site on to their computers hard drive, you should take the necessary steps within your web browserâs settings to block all cookies from the Site. Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain parts of our Site may not function correctly. For information on how to disable cookies, refer to your browserâs documentation.

Cookies and our advertisers: Advertisers on our website may set cookies and you should refer directly to an advertisers website for details on their cookies and privacy policy. Their cookies may be set while you surf our site, by virtue of the advertisement being placed in an iframe.

Retaining and Deleting Personal Data: We will retain your Personal Data for as long as long as you maintain an account or subscription agreement or as otherwise necessary to provide you the Services. We will also retain your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Users may request the deletion of their account by contacting us.  
We will retain and delete your personal data as follows:  
\- We will delete all personal data 30 days after the approval of your account deletion request.  
\- Your communication data with other members will be deleted 5 years after you delete your account.

Notwithstanding the other provisions, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

General. We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply.

How to Contact us. The data controller responsible for your personal data for is Mondinion SRL, a Romania limited liability company; address 37, V. Lucaciu street, Satu Mare, Romania. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, your rights and/or our data collection practices, please contact our customer support.
